let's continue our ongoing quiz this
instruction has issued we have issued it
in cycle 1 it begins executing in cycle
2 because these operands are ready the
result is gonna be 20 over 5 so the
result is gonna be four and that result
will become available in 2 plus 10 that
result will be broadcast in cycle 12 and
this makes us ready to begin cycle 2 at
the beginning of cycle 2 this
reservation station is already freed and
we will try to issue this instruction
that instruction will be issued by
finding a reservation station and a row
up entry we will write to our 1 hour 5
in our 6 are gonna come from the
register file gonna be 4 + 2 the result
will be broadcast under the name of Rob
2 and we have issued this instruction in
cycle 2 in cycle 2 also the execution of
this instruction of the first
instruction has began in cycle 3 we will
issue the next instruction and begin
executing this one so what happens in
cycle 4 is we have issued this
instruction its operands were ready
already so at the beginning of cycle for
this reservation station is free that
instruction has began execution and we
will consider now issuing this
multiplication here the question for you
regarding this multiplication is what is
going to be here here here and here
so what is going to be in the
reservation station for the
multiplication once we have issued it
and we do issue it in the fourth cycle
and also which rat entry put the
register number is going to be modified
as a result of this so which rat entry
is it R 1 R 2 R 3 or which one